sha la la some day in the future
sha la la itsuka kitto
I will for sure hold it in my hand
boku wa te ni suru nda
it will softly set ablaze
hakanaki mune ni sotto
a light in my empty heart
hikari moeteyuke
the "impulses" that makes you want to meet it
aitaku naru no shoudou
the "innocence" that makes you want to cry
nakitaku naru no junjou
they've gone into the summer fire
natsu no hi ni tobikonda
the fireflies aren't coming back
hotaru wa kaeranai
you didn't say a single word and left a kiss for me behind
anata wa nanimo iwazu kuchizuke wo nokoshite
and nodded as you still got burned
kitsuzuku mama unazuita ne
it was so sad that my life was wavering
kanashii hodo inochi yurameiteita
sha la la some day in the future
sha la la itsuka kitto
I will for sure hold it in my hand
boku wa te ni suru nda
it will softly set ablaze
hakanaki mune ni sotto
a light in my empty heart
hikari moeteyuke
sha la la my sweet lovely dear
sha la la itoshiki hito
I can also see you right now
anata mo mieteiru no
the dazzling moon will softly
mabayui tsuki ga sotto
illuminate the morning day
ashita wo terashite
and strongly and strongly shine on
tsuyoku tsuyoku kagayaite
うお～っ！
ふん！
うわっ…。
The small fry can stay out of this!
ザコは 引っ込んでな！
さあ かかってきな カカシ。
All right! Come at me, Kakashi!
Breaking the Crystal Style
Hide my face, but not my butt!
(トビ)頭隠して 尻隠さず。
(トビ)あん？
Oh?
I'm a schoolgirl in love
with her Senpai!
先輩に思いを寄せる女子高生。
O-Oh? Hey Senpai!
Are you still angry?
あ あら？ ちょっと先輩！
まだ怒ってるんですか？
Let's be friends and
look for Three-Tail's together.
仲よく 一緒に
三尾探しましょうよ！
Get lost!
(デイダラ)失せろ！
But if we don't get to work,
the others will chew us out.
だって 仕事しないと➡
他の先輩に
また怒られちゃいますよ！
Please give me a break.
もう 許してくださいよ～。
I know! I'll let you take
a special peek inside the mask.
あっ そうだ！ 仮面の中
特別に見せちゃいます。
I said get lost!
失せろと言ってるんだ！
Oh Senpai! I just might go somewhere
for real if you say it like that!
もう先輩！
そんなこと言うと➡
ホント どっか行っちゃいますよ！
I have no choice...
ああ もう しようがないな。
I'll go search by myself for a while.
しばらくは １人で探すか。
そりゃっ！
So this is the power
she kept hidden...
《これが ヤツが秘めていた力か》
So persistent...
あきらめの悪い…。
And when your ink drawing
doesn't work, you run away...
墨絵が効かないと
後は逃げるだけ。
Is that your Ninja Art?
それが お前の忍法か。
There are other uses for my ink.
ボクの墨の使い方は
それだけじゃない。
What...?
なに…。
うおぉ！
Ninja Art: Ink Flush.
忍法 墨流し。
What's the matter?
さぁ どうした？
かかってきなよ！
Come at me!
I'm fed up...
《まいったね…
コイツ前に戦ったときは➡
When we last fought,
she didn't release all her power?
まだ すべての力を
出していなかったのか》
チッ！ 次は 本気を出すよ！
The next one's for real!
Crystal Style:
Burst Crystal Falling Dragon!
晶遁！ 破晶降龍！
Wha--?!
なに!?
死にな！
Die!
She can turn anything
she touches into crystal.
《コイツは 接触する
あらゆる物質を結晶化させる。
In other words, Water, Earth
nor Wood Styles have any effect.
つまり 水遁 土遁 木遁は
効果がない。
However... this will...!
しかし これなら！》
やったか!?
Did I do it...?
So naïve...
甘いね！
ぐおっ!!
Too bad, Kakashi.
残念だったね カカシ。
The three-tailed dragon was
just a diversion to keep me here...
三匹の龍は オレを
移動させないための目くらましか。
For all the talk I've heard,
your Sharingan isn't much.
なんだかんだ言っても➡
大したことないね
写輪眼のカカシも。
Well now, playtime is over.
もう遊びは終わりだよ。
It's useless.
ムダだ。
うが～っ！
Now then, where is it, where is it?
(トビ)さ～て
どこかな？ どこかな？
Actually, where should I go...
っていうか どこに行くかな…。
Huh?
ん？
I've discovered an awfully suspicious lake!
なんか むちゃくちゃ
怪しい湖 発見。
Hmm?
What're they doing anyway?
何やってんだ？ アイツら。
They're from the Hidden Leaf...
あれは 木ノ葉の…。
キャッ！
H-Hey!
ちょっと！
いの！
Ino... focus on the Chakra
for the barrier!
結界を張るチャクラに集中して！
は… はい！
R-Right!
Barrier? Hey no way...
That's impossible.
結界？ ヘッ！ まさか。
いや まさか まさか。
ん？ あらら…
もう一匹いるけど➡
Huh?
Oh my... There's another one...
But I've never seen him before.
見たことねえな…。
《麟児 : 木ノ葉の連中
三尾を見つけだすつもりか？》
The Hidden Leaf...
are looking for Three-Tails?
ハッ！ まぁ 高見の見物といくか。
Oh well...
I guess I'll just sit back and watch.
Okay, let's settle this!
さ～て…
そろそろ 決着をつけるよ！
カカシ先生！
Kakashi-sensei...!
Prepare to die...!
覚悟しな！
What?!
なにっ!?
Oh! Shino!
シノ！
Just in the nick of time.
Are they ready?
間一髪ってところだね。
できたのか？
If they weren't, I wouldn't have come.
できていなければ
ここには来ない。
Humph... If it isn't the Insect user.
ふぅ… 誰かと思えば 蟲使いかい。
Your Jutsu is useless against me.
お前の術じゃ
私に通用しないよ！
It's useless!
ムダなんだよ！
Didn't I tell you? It's useless.
だから 言っただろう？ ムダだって。
それはどうかな。
I wonder about that...
What?!
なに!?
It can't be!
バカな…！
Your Jutsu won't work against me.
お前の術は
もう オレには効かない。
And that's because
my insects can evolve limitlessly.
なぜなら オレの蟲は
無限の進化を遂げる。
お前の術への耐性は得た。
They are now resistant to your Jutsu.
Yes, you did it! That's amazing!
よし やった！ すげぇぞ！
That's impossible...
My Crystal Style can't be defeated...
ありえない…
私の晶遁が やぶれるなんて…。
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
多重影分身の術！
I won't let you get away now!
もう 逃がしゃしねぇってばよ！
Stay still!
(カカシ)おとなしくしろ。
Where is Yuukimaru?!
幽鬼丸は どこにいる!?
なんで お前…。 あ！
Why do you...?!
お前だって
あの子の力が欲しいんだろ？
You want that boy's power too?
I don't need anything like that!
オレは そんなもんいらねえ！
どうだかな。
I wonder about that...
あぁっ！
Now...! Her Crystal Style
has been sealed!
(シノ)今だ！
ヤツの晶遁は封じられた。
Tell us!
白状しやがれ！
幽鬼丸は どこだ!?
Where is Yuukimaru?!
この！
Why you--!
これは！
This is...!
紅蓮さん…。
Guren-san...
これは… 泥!?
This is... mud?
どうやら あの結晶は
すぐ修復するようだ。
It seems that Crystal
mends itself right away.
クソ！ やっても やっても
きりがねえ！
Damn it! There's no end to this!
蟲の攻撃を一点に集中させろ！
Focus the Insects' attack on one spot.
紅蓮さん…。
Guren-san...
《間に合わない！》
I can't keep up...!
雷切！
Lightning Blade!
泥の壁!?
A mud wall?!
牛頭!?
Gozu?!
牛頭… お前！
Gozu, you...
何しやがる!? 放せ！
What're you doing?!
Let go! I'm going to kill them...!
私は ヤツらにとどめを…。
牛頭…。
Gozu...?
ここは通さない！
I won't let you through!
うぅ…。
紅蓮さん！
Guren-san!
大丈夫か!? カカシ先生！
あぁ。
Are you all right, Kakashi-sensei?!
Yeah... But...
だが 紅蓮には逃げられた。
くっ！
Guren got away.
幽鬼丸の居場所をつきとめる
手がかりだったのに。
She was the key to finding Yuukimaru...!
残念だ。 なぜなら➡
It's regrettable...
My insects performed flawlessly,
yet she got away...
オレの蟲は 完璧に働いたのに➡
逃げられたからだ。
いいか？ 手分けして探す。
All right, we'll split up and search!
ナルトはシノと。 サイはオレについて来い。
Naruto, you go with Shino.
Sai, come with me!
みなさんが
すごいヤツらだって煽るから➡
You said that they were formidable,
闘志を燃やしていたんですが…。
so I was burning with the desire to fight...
何あれ？ 全然じゃない。
What was that?
They were so easy to beat.
ああ。
この間と別人みたいだったぜ。
Yup... They were so different
from the last time.
他のヤツらも
前評判だけじゃないの？
Are you real sure about these
next guys?
油断しないように。
はい。
Don't let your guard down.
Y-Yes!
カカシ先輩が苦戦したくらいだ。
Kakashi-senpai had
his hands full with her.
晶遁使いは本物だよ。
The Crystal Style user is no joke!
ボクの体術が通じるか
ぜひ 手合わせしたいものです。
I'd love to face her in battle...
to see if my Taijutsu is effective
against her!
ここで二手に別れよう。
Let's split up into two groups here.
リーとテンテンは
湖面の封印班の警護を。
Lee and Tenten will guard
the Sealing team by the lake!
我々は 先輩の対晶遁班と➡
And we will join up with Senpai's team
who are battling the Crystal Style user!
合流する。
はい。
Right!
ええ！
晶遁使いと戦えないんですか？
Huh? I won't be able to fight
the Crystal Style user?
敵は どこに現れるか わからない。
We don't know where
the enemy may appear.
油断するなと言ったはずだよ。
I just told you not to
let your guard down...!
(リー/テンテン)は はい！
- Y-Yes!
- Yes!
"SEARCH"
あっ 今…。
Huh?! Just now...!
わかってる。 この近く…。
I know... It's close...
この真下にいる。
Directly below us...
いよいよね。
It's finally come...
(シズネ)結界四方封陣を
「探」のモードから切り替える。
We are switching from the "search" mode
of the Four-Corner Sealing Barrier.
息を乱さないで。 いくわよ。
Keep your breathing soft and steady.
Here we go!
(みんな)結界四方封陣 「縛」！
- Four-Corner Sealing Barrier: Bind!
BIND
このまま 網を静かに沈めていく。
We'll quietly sink the net.
Do not let the Three-Tails detect us!
三尾に気配を気取られるな。
ちょっと先輩 やっぱ三尾ですよ！
って いないんですよ。
Oh no, Senpai!
It is the Three Tails, after all...!
Right, he's not here...
ん？
Huh?!
(トビ)アイツ 止めるつもりか？
Does he intend to stop them?
敵が！
(サクラたち)えっ!?
The enemy...!
(シズネ)気を乱すな。
(いの)でも…。
Concentrate!
But!
木ノ葉旋風！
Leaf Hurricane!
なに!?
What?!
リーさん。 テンテンさん。
Lee! Tenten!
向こうの敵が終わったんで
急いで駆けつけてきました。
We've taken care of
the enemy on that side,
so we rushed over.
間に合ってよかったです。
I'm glad we made it in time!
ボクが来たからには この４人に
指一本 触れさせません。
Now that I'm here,
I won't allow you to lay
a finger on these four!
お前たちは
足止めしてあったはずだ。
There should've been others to stop you...
ああ 彼らですか？
Oh, them...
They were no match for us.
ボクたちの敵じゃありませんね。
く… 鬼霧たちが敗れたのか。
Damn... So Kigiri and
the others were beaten...
さぁ ボクが相手します。
Now then, I am your opponent!
チッ…。
(テンテン)なによ 逃げるの!?
What? Running away?!
(トビ)あらららら やばい やばいよ。
Uh-oh... This is bad. Real bad!
このままじゃ
三尾封印されちゃうじゃん。
At this rate,
the Three-Tails will be sealed!
でも 今出てっても
やられちゃうかな？
But if I go out now, I might lose.
I'm outnumbered.
向こう人数多いし… ねぇ 先輩？
Right, Senpai? And he's not here...
…って いない。
《カブト : フン… どいつも こいつも
使えないヤツばかりだな。
Humph...
Useless, the whole lot of them.
木ノ葉の術式は 三尾の封印。
The Hidden Leaf ritual aims
to seal the Three-Tails.
三尾を誰にも利用されない道を
選んだのか…。
They've chosen a path
which will prevent anyone
from using the Three-Tails.
そうは させられない》
But I won't allow that.
(カブト)幽鬼丸？
Yuukimaru...?
紅蓮さん…。
Guren-san...
《イヤだ… 白い椿は
赤い椿になっちゃダメなんだ…。
No... The white camellia
cannot become a red one.
約束だよ… 帰ってきて》
You promised... that you'll come back!
ゴ… 牛頭… お前…。
Gozu... You...
♪♪(草笛)
((幽鬼丸？
Yuukimaru...?
(はっ!? キャア!!))
♪♪(草笛)
こ… この草笛は…。
No! This grass whistle...
まさか… まさか… まさか…。
No way...
No way... It's impossible...
あっ…。
♪♪(草笛)
うわぁ～!!
《私が… あの子の母親を
殺したというのか!?
Did I kill that boy's mother...?!
そんな… そんな!?》
That's... That's...!
(カブト)紅蓮。
あっ!?
Guren...
行くぞ。
お前 大蛇丸様のところに➡
We must go.
You?! I thought you returned
to Orochimaru-sama.
帰ったんじゃないのか!?
それどころじゃなくなった。
There's something more pressing.
木ノ葉の封印術に
三尾が かかってしまってね。
The Hidden Leaf has started
to seal the Three-Tails.
なんだと!?
幽鬼丸を使って三尾を操る。
What?
We'll use Yuukimaru to
control the Three-Tails.
そして ヤツらの結界を破るんだ。
And we'll destroy their barrier.
カブト 話がある。
Kabuto, I need to talk to you.
なんだ この時間のないときに…。
What, at a time like this?
わかってる。
だが これ以上 力を使わせれば➡
I know that.
But you of all people should know
what would happen
幽鬼丸が どうなるか
アンタなら わかるはずだ！
if we make Yuukimaru use
his powers any further...
なんだ そんなことか…。
Huh? Is that all?
本当のことを話せ！
Tell me the truth!
(カブト)何を カッカしてる。
Why're you so upset?
幽鬼丸が生きようと生きまいと
お前には 関係があるまい。
It's none of your business
whether Yuukimaru lives or dies.
関係は… ある。
It is... my business.
Oh? So even the devil sheds tears?
ほぉ～ 鬼の目にも涙
というわけか。
これまで数え切れないほど
人を殺してきたお前が➡
To think that you,
who have killed countless people,
幽鬼丸に情を寄せるとはね。
would have a soft spot for Yuukimaru.
これは驚きだ。
(紅蓮)あの子は特別だ！
Now that is a surprise.
He's special...
あの子の母親を殺したからか？
どうして それを？
Because you killed his mother?
How did you...?
別に不思議じゃない。
There's nothing unusual about that.
大蛇丸様は すべて お見通しだ。
It's as Orochimaru-sama predicted.
お前があの子に転ぶってこともね。
He knew that you would
have feelings for the boy.
だからこそ お前を選んだ。
That's exactly why he chose you.
なんなら ボクから幽鬼丸に
教えてあげてもいいんだけどね。
If you like,
I can tell Yuukimaru for you...
唯一 帰る場所だと信じていた
優しい紅蓮さんは➡
That the kind, gentle Guren-san
whom he believes
is the one he should return to...
自分の母親を殺した
極悪人だったってね。
is the evil villain who killed his mother...
やめろ！
Stop!
Then, carry out my orders.
なら ボクの命令に
素直に従うんだね。
テンテン いつまた
敵が来るか わかりません。
Tenten...
We don't know when
the enemy will appear again.
油断しないでください。
Please stay alert.
よく なつかせたものだ。
You endeared him to you very skillfully...
ウフフ ウフフ…！
《カブト : 大蛇丸様 悔しいが➡
Orochimaru-sama...
I hate to admit it,
but you were right to select that woman...
あの女を選んだのは
間違っていませんでしたよ》
((カブト : 紅蓮が
幽鬼丸に情を寄せる？
Guren will grow to love Yuukimaru?
Is that even possible?
そんなことがあるのですか？
(大蛇丸)フッ… カブト
お前も まだまだね。
Kabuto, you have much to learn.
同じ時をすごせば すごすほど
絆は深くなる。
The more time you spend with someone,
the stronger the bond becomes.
人間とは そういうものよ。
That is human nature.
そうでしょうか。
Is that so...?
(大蛇丸)あの２人は
深い因縁で結ばれている。
Those two...
Their ties go deep indeed.
おそらく 紅蓮は
私の命令を忘れて裏切るわ。
It's likely that Guren will disobey
my order and betray me.
(そのときは…))
Then...
《カブト : そろそろ 頃合いですかね
大蛇丸様…》
I guess that time has come...
Orochimaru-sama...
before the reality of a deep breath
sonzai to shinkokyuu no genjitsu wo mae ni
my gaze my very existence tries to challenge it
idomou to suru shisen wa
mistakes are made and in the confusion of it all everything burns into my mind
machigai mo tomadoi mo zenbu yaki tsukeru
in a series of moments
isshun no renzoku no naka de
beyond a great number of promises
ikutsu mono yakusoku no sono ue ni tatte wa
are the words that spilled over from the day as I reflect upon them
kamishimeru ano hi koboreochita kotoba
it's as though I made a vow which expresses these feelings into words
komerareta omoi wa chikai no you de
then it would link the befinning with the present day
kuchi ni sureba ima to hajimari wo tsunagu
it's not in my dreams
yume de wa nakute
that place doesn't exist in a fantasy world either
esoragoto no sekai de mo nai basho de sa
before the reality of a deep breath
sonzai to shinkokyuu no genjitsu no mae ni
my gaze my very existence tries to challenge it
idomou to suru shisen wa
mistakes are made and in the confusion of it all everything burns into my mind
machigai mo tomadoi mo zenbu yaki tsukete
embracing the long path ahead
sono zutto saki wo toraeru
in a series of moments
isshun no renzoku no naka de
Next Episode
Sai, how is it?
Still no reaction to
the Crystal Style user.
She used up considerable Chakra
during that last battle.
Now is the time to strike.
I don't want to give her too much time.
I agree. I'm going to widen
the scope of my search.
Damn it! Where'd she disappear to?!
Naruto, patience is the key.
I know!
But the boy...
I'll find him for sure.
The Battle Over
the Barrier
Next time: "The Battle Over the Barrier"